<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<application>
 <id type="desktop">photocollage.desktop</id>
 <metadata_license>CC-BY-3.0</metadata_license>
 <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
 <name>PhotoCollage</name>
 <summary>Graphical tool to make photo collage posters</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="cs">Grafický nástroj pro vytváření koláží z fotografií</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="de">Grafisches Werkzeug zum erstellen von Foto-Collagen Poster</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="fr">Outil graphique pour fabriquer des posters en collant plusieurs photos</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="it">Strumento grafico per creare collage di fotografie</summary>
 <description>
  <p>
   PhotoCollage allows you to create photo collage posters. It assembles the
   input photographs it is given to generate a big poster. Photos are
   automatically arranged to fill the whole poster, then you can change the
   final layout, dimensions, border or swap photos in the generated grid.
   Eventually the final poster image can be saved in any size.
  </p>
  <p>
   The algorithm generates random layouts that place photos while taking
   advantage of all free space. It tries to fill all space while keeping each
   photo as large as possible.
  </p>
  <p>
   PhotoCollage does more or less the same as many commercial websites do, but
   for free and with open-source code.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="cs">
   PhotoCollage umožnuje vytvářet koláž z obrázků. Z vybraných fotografií je
   vygenerována velká pohlednice. Fotografie jsou automaticky velikostně
   upraveny, tak aby zaplnily celou pohlednici. Výsledné uspořádání, velikost,
   rámeček nebo umístění fotografií lze změnit. Výslednou pohlednici lze uložit
   libovolné velikosti.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="cs">
   Algoritmus generuje náhodné rozložení, fotografie jsou rozprostřeny přes
   veškeré volné místo. Program se snaží umístit fotografie v co největším
   formátu při zaplnění veškerého volného místa.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="cs">
   PhotoCollage dělá více méně to samé co mnoho komerčních webových portálů,
   ale PhotoCollage je zdarma a open-source.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="de">
   PhotoCollage erlaubt Ihnen das Erstellen von Foto-Collage Postern. 
   Ausgewählte Fotos werden automatisch auf einer rechteckigen
   Posterfläche arrangiert. Es ist möglich, Anordnung sowie Abmessungen der 
   Fotos und des Rahmens zu bearbeiten und Fotos auszutauschen.
   Das fertige Poster kann in beliebiger Größe gespeichert werden.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="de">
   Das zugrundeligende Rechenverfahren erzeugt die Anordnung bei größtmöglicher 
   Ausnutzung der Posterfläche in der Weise, dass jedes Foto so groß wie möglich
   dargestellt wird.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="de">
   Der Funktionsumfang von PhotoCollage entspricht etwa dem vieler kommerzieller
   Webseiten. Jedoch ist es kostenlos und der Quellcode unter einer freien 
   Lizenz erhältlich.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="fr">
   PhotoCollage permet de créer des posters de photo-collages. Il assemble les
   photos qu'on lui donne pour générer un grand poster. Les photos sont
   automatiquement arrangées pour remplir le poster entièrement ; vous pouvez
   ensuite changer la structure finale, les dimensions, les bordures ou
   intervertir des photos dans le maillage généré. Finalement le poster final
   peut être sauvegardé en n'importe quelle résolution.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="fr">
   L'algorithme place les photos dans un maillage généré aléatoirement, en
   remplissant l'espace libre. Il essaie de ne laisser aucun trou, tout en
   gardant chaque photo aussi grande que possible.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="fr">
   PhotoCollage fait plus ou moins ce que beaucoup de sites web commerciaux
   font, mais gratuitement et avec du code open-source.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="it">
   PhotoCollage permette di creare poster da collage di fotografie.
   Assembla le fotografie che vengono inserite per generare un poster. Le
   immagini vengono posizionate automaticamente per riempire interamente il
   poster; in seguito è possibile modificare la struttura finale, le
   dimensioni, i bordi o scambiare le fotografie nella griglia generata. Il
   risultato finale può essere salvato in qualsiasi dimensione.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="it">
   L’algoritmo posiziona le immagini in una griglia generata casualmente,
   riempiendo lo spazio libero. Cerca di non lasciare alcun buco, mantenendo
   ogni fotografia la più grande possibile.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="it">
   PhotoCollage fa più o meno quello che fanno molti siti web commerciali, ma
   gratuitamente e con codice open source.
  </p>
 </description>
 <screenshots>
  <screenshot type="default" width="800" height="450">
   https://github.com/adrienverge/PhotoCollage/raw/v1.4.0/screenshots/photocollage-1.4-preview.png
  </screenshot>
 </screenshots>
 <url type="homepage">https://github.com/adrienverge/PhotoCollage</url>
 <updatecontact>adrienverge_at_gmail.com</updatecontact>
</application>
