<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop">
 <id>photocollage.desktop</id>
 <metadata_license>CC-BY-3.0</metadata_license>
 <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
 <name>PhotoCollage</name>
 <developer_name>Adrien Vergé</developer_name>
 <launchable type="desktop-id">photocollage.desktop</launchable>
 <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
 <summary>Graphical tool to make photo collage posters</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="cs">Grafický nástroj pro vytváření koláží z fotografií</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="de">Grafisches Werkzeug zum erstellen von Foto-Collagen Poster</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="es">Herramienta gráfica para hacer póster de collage de fotos.</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="fr">Outil graphique pour fabriquer des posters en collant plusieurs photos</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="it">Strumento grafico per creare collage di fotografie</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="nl">Grafische toepassing om fotocollageposters te maken</summary>
<summary xml:lang="pt-br">Ferramenta gráfica para fazer pôsteres de colagem de fotos</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="ru">Графический инструмент для создания фотоколлажей</summary>
 <summary xml:lang="uk">Графічний застосунок для створення фотоколажів</summary>
 <description>
  <p>
   PhotoCollage allows you to create photo collage posters. It assembles the
   input photographs it is given to generate a big poster. Photos are
   automatically arranged to fill the whole poster, then you can change the
   final layout, dimensions, border or swap photos in the generated grid.
   Eventually the final poster image can be saved in any size.
  </p>
  <p>
   The algorithm generates random layouts that place photos while taking
   advantage of all free space. It tries to fill all space while keeping each
   photo as large as possible.
  </p>
  <p>
   PhotoCollage does more or less the same as many commercial websites do, but
   for free and with open-source code.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="cs">
   PhotoCollage umožnuje vytvářet koláž z obrázků. Z vybraných fotografií je
   vygenerována velká pohlednice. Fotografie jsou automaticky velikostně
   upraveny, tak aby zaplnily celou pohlednici. Výsledné uspořádání, velikost,
   rámeček nebo umístění fotografií lze změnit. Výslednou pohlednici lze uložit
   libovolné velikosti.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="cs">
   Algoritmus generuje náhodné rozložení, fotografie jsou rozprostřeny přes
   veškeré volné místo. Program se snaží umístit fotografie v co největším
   formátu při zaplnění veškerého volného místa.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="cs">
   PhotoCollage dělá více méně to samé co mnoho komerčních webových portálů,
   ale PhotoCollage je zdarma a open-source.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="de">
   PhotoCollage erlaubt Ihnen das Erstellen von Foto-Collage Postern. 
   Ausgewählte Fotos werden automatisch auf einer rechteckigen
   Posterfläche arrangiert. Es ist möglich, Anordnung sowie Abmessungen der 
   Fotos und des Rahmens zu bearbeiten und Fotos auszutauschen.
   Das fertige Poster kann in beliebiger Größe gespeichert werden.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="de">
   Das zugrundeligende Rechenverfahren erzeugt die Anordnung bei größtmöglicher 
   Ausnutzung der Posterfläche in der Weise, dass jedes Foto so groß wie möglich
   dargestellt wird.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="de">
   Der Funktionsumfang von PhotoCollage entspricht etwa dem vieler kommerzieller
   Webseiten. Jedoch ist es kostenlos und der Quellcode unter einer freien 
   Lizenz erhältlich.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="es">
   PhotoCollage te permite crear póster de collage de fotos. Reúne las 
   fotografías de entrada que se le dan para generar un gran póster. Las 
   fotos se organizan automáticamente para llenar todo el póster, luego 
   puede cambiar el diseño final, las dimensiones, los bordes o intercambiar 
   fotos en la cuadrícula generada. Finalmente, la imagen final del póster 
   se puede guardar en cualquier tamaño.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="es">
   El algoritmo genera diseños aleatorios que colocan fotos mientras 
   aprovechan todo el espacio libre. Intenta llenar todo el espacio 
   manteniendo cada foto lo más grande posible.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="es">
   PhotoCollage hace más o menos lo mismo que muchos sitios web comerciales, 
   pero de forma gratuita y con código de open source.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="fr">
   PhotoCollage permet de créer des posters de photo-collages. Il assemble les
   photos qu'on lui donne pour générer un grand poster. Les photos sont
   automatiquement arrangées pour remplir le poster entièrement ; vous pouvez
   ensuite changer la structure finale, les dimensions, les bordures ou
   intervertir des photos dans le maillage généré. Finalement le poster final
   peut être sauvegardé en n'importe quelle résolution.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="fr">
   L'algorithme place les photos dans un maillage généré aléatoirement, en
   remplissant l'espace libre. Il essaie de ne laisser aucun trou, tout en
   gardant chaque photo aussi grande que possible.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="fr">
   PhotoCollage fait plus ou moins ce que beaucoup de sites web commerciaux
   font, mais gratuitement et avec du code open-source.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="it">
   PhotoCollage permette di creare poster da collage di fotografie.
   Assembla le fotografie che vengono inserite per generare un poster. Le
   immagini vengono posizionate automaticamente per riempire interamente il
   poster; in seguito è possibile modificare la struttura finale, le
   dimensioni, i bordi o scambiare le fotografie nella griglia generata. Il
   risultato finale può essere salvato in qualsiasi dimensione.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="it">
   L’algoritmo posiziona le immagini in una griglia generata casualmente,
   riempiendo lo spazio libero. Cerca di non lasciare alcun buco, mantenendo
   ogni fotografia la più grande possibile.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="it">
   PhotoCollage fa più o meno quello che fanno molti siti web commerciali, ma
   gratuitamente e con codice open source.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="nl">
   Met PhotoCollage kun je collageposters maken. Alle opgegeven
   afbeeldingen worden samengevoegd tot één grote poster: ze worden
   automatisch ingedeeld om de gehele poster op te vullen. Daarna kun je de
   indeling, afmetingen, randdikte en volgorde aanpassen en de poster opslaan
   in elke denkbare grootte.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="pt-br">
   Photocollage permite criar pôsteres de colagem de fotos. Ele reune
   fotografias de entrada para gerar um grande pôster. As
   As fotos são organizadas automaticamente para preencher o pôster inteiro
   então, você pode alterar o design final, dimensões, bordas ou trocar
   fotos na grade gerada.Finalmente, a imagem final do pôster
   pode ser salva em qualquer tamanho.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="pt-br">
   O algoritmo gera layouts aleatórios das fotos
   aproveitando todo o espaço livre. Ele Tenta preencher todo o espaço
   Mantendo cada foto o maior possível.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="pt-br">
   Photocollage faz mais ou menos o mesmo que muitos sites comerciais,
   porém, de graça e com código aberto.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="ru">
   PhotoCollage позволяет создавать фотоколлажи. Из данных ему
   фотографий он генерирует большой постер. Фотографии автоматически
   заполняют всё полотно, затем можно изменить окончательный макет, 
   размеры, границы или поменять местами фотографии в сгенерированной сетке.
   Окончательное изображение можно сохранить в любом размере.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="ru">
   Алгоритм генерирует случайные макеты, размещающие фотографии 
   на всём доступном пространстве. Он старается заполнить всё полотно так, 
   чтобы у каждой фотографии был наибольший возможный размер.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="ru">
   PhotoCollage делает более или менее то же самое, что и многие 
   коммерческие веб-сайты, но бесплатно и с открытым исходным кодом.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="uk">
   PhotoCollage дозволяє створювати фотоколажі. З отриманих
   світлин він генерує великий постер. Світлини автоматично
   заповнюють все полотно, потім можна змінити кінцевий макет,
   розміри, межі або поміняти місцями світлини в згенерованій сітці.
   Фінальне зображення можна зберегти в будь-якому розмірі.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="uk">
   Алгоритм генерує випадкові макети що розміщують світлини на всьому
   доступному просторі. Він намагається заповнити все полотно так,
   щоб у кожної світлини був найбільший можливий розмір.
  </p>
  <p xml:lang="uk">
   PhotoCollage робить більш-менш те саме що комерційні сайти,
   але безкоштовно і з відкритим початковим кодом.
  </p>
 </description>
 <screenshots>
  <screenshot type="default" width="800" height="450">
   <image>https://github.com/adrienverge/PhotoCollage/raw/v1.4.0/screenshots/photocollage-1.4-preview.png</image>
  </screenshot>
 </screenshots>
 <url type="homepage">https://github.com/adrienverge/PhotoCollage</url>
 <url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/adrienverge/PhotoCollage/issues</url>
 <url type="vcs-browser">https://github.com/adrienverge/PhotoCollage</url>
 <url type="translate">https://github.com/adrienverge/PhotoCollage/tree/master/po</url>
 <update_contact>adrienverge_at_gmail.com</update_contact>
 <releases>
   <release version="1.4.5" date="2021-07-09" />
 </releases>
</component>
